(conversation, laughter)
Thank you.
Wow. She's cute.
She sure is.
She sucks
in bed.
And not in a good way.
Her, too?
I-I didn't even know
she was gay.
Neither did she,
till last Thursday.
You're like some
kind of lesbian zombie
infecting all
the women of Malibu.
Ha!
I like that.
(as zombie):
Must have vagina.
Sounds like some kind of
weird help wanted ad
Alan would place.
(chuckles)
So when did you realize
that you were gay?
Oh, oh...
What's that I hear?
Is that your own closet door
finally swinging open?
Trust me,
if I was gay
you'd be the first
one to know.
You know, I think I was
in high school
when I figured it out.
A bunch of my friends
were having a sleepover
and we started talking about
what it would be like
to kiss a boy
and who was the best kisser.
So me and my friend Kimberly,
who was a cheerleader,
decided to settle it
by making out.
A-a cheerleader?
Let the woman talk.
Kimberly was so hot.
I still remember
how soft her lips felt
as she slipped
her hand under my shirt
and kissed her way down my body.
Must've been a strange and
confusing time for you.
Please continue.
She closed her eyes.
She parted her lips.
She arched her back
and I whispered in her ear,
"Oh, my God,
"Kimberly,
"I can't believe
"these two idiots
actually believe this story."
And then what happe...
Aw!
Damn it!
It's not that complicated.
The first time you masturbate
thinking about the school nurse
you pretty much know.
BOTH:
Oh, my God, I'm a lesbian.
We need to start hanging out with
girls who aren't gay.
Or related to us.
How 'bout her?
Oh, I suppose I could
go talk to her.
I think Jenny was
talking about me.
Oh, really?
And you assume that just because
you're rich and good-looking?
No, I was going to say
smart and charming,
but if you mix all those
ingredients together,
you make one delicious
hot guy pie.
Well, your "hot guy pie"
is no match for my system.
No, hold on.
Going on Craigslist
and looking up "escorts"
isn't a system.
That is not my system,
that is my backup plan.
My system consists
of the three "C"s:
connect, charm and cry.
Works every time.
Uh, okay...
"Hi, my name's Alan.
"That is a beautiful
blouse you're wearing.
My dead wife was buried
in one just like it."
Yeah, my system's
a lot simpler.
I wait for you
to finish talking
and then I
take them home.
Oh, oh, big words
coming from somebody
sitting alone next to me.
Oh.
Okay, fine. Well, let's just go see
who she likes better.
Oh, my God.
No one is safe.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x07 ♪
Some Kind of Lesbian Zombie
Original Air Date on November 14, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(indistinct conversations)
Hey, do you think all women
are potentially lesbians?
Um, I have 30 years
of masturbating to porn
that say yes.
You know,
you brag more
about your
masturbating prowess
than any person
I know.
It ain't bragging
if it's true.
Ooh. Alpha bravo,
two bogeys on your six.
Why are you
talking like that?
Oh, my...
Did you have a stroke?
It's airplane talk.
I'm your wingman.
It... it just means two cute girls
just walked in.
Why didn't you just say
two cute girls just walked in?
Roger that.
Will you stop that?
Over and out.
Wow.
Yeah.
They are cute.
Yeah, yeah.
So, uh... so what's
the play here?
Um, uh... how about
something like, uh...
"Hey, uh, those
seats are taken,
but our faces aren't"?
How about,
"I'm Walden,
and this is my
mute friend Alan"?
Fine.
You think you've got such
great game, lead the way,
Mr. "I'm too good for
Craigslist and masturbating."
Hi.
That's all I got.
Uh, ladies, uh, uh, how much does
a polar bear weigh?
Oh, I don't know.
Enough to break the ice.
I'm Dr. Alan Harper.
Uh, this is my associate
Walden Schmidt.
Google him,
he's rich.
If you Google me,
you can see my boobs.
Also if you do this.
Hi.
Oh, oh, uh,
take another look,
but this time
spell "attic."
A-T-T-I-C.
Oh! I get it.
Because these are my tee-tees
and I see them.
I'm sorry about my friend.
Walden.
Jill.
So, Alan, what kind of
doctor are you?
Oh, I'm a...
a chiropractor...
slash brain surgeon.
Oh!
So, uh, w-what do
you guys do?
We're princesses
at a theme park.
Really?
Yeah, I play
Cinderella
and she's the
Little Mermaid.
Oh, well, that
certainly makes sense
because, uh,
you "swept"
my friend
off his feet
and-and I'm
"hooked" on you.
Oh, my God,
that's funny
because I'm a fish.
(laughing)
Yes.
The answer to the question
you're not asking is:
because she makes
me look smart.
Well, the answer to the question
you're not asking is:
because he won't
move out.
Morning.
Oh, hey.
How great
was last night?
It was pretty good.
Those girls didn't know
what hit 'em.
What'd you use,
chloroform or Tasers?
I will have you know
that Walden and I
have dates tonight
with two theme park princesses.
Mine's Cinderella.
Perfect for you.
Storybook beauty.
And mine is the Little Mermaid.
Perfect for you.
No legs to run away.
I'm telling you,
if we play our cards right,
we're gonna get ourselves
some fairy-tail.
"Fairy-tail"?
Because, you know,
"tail" has two meanings.
Yeah, so does "fairy."
Hey, guys.
ALAN: Hi.
Hey.
This is Maria.
Maria, this is Walden
and Alan.
Oh, that's so cool.
You didn't tell me
your parents were gay.
Didn't I?
Dad and Mom.
Hi.
It's nice to meet you.
Uh, listen,
I gotta go.
But you are going
to call me, right?
Absolutely.
You sure?
Yes.
I would not lie to you
in front of my parents.
Bye, it was nice meeting you.
Don't be a stranger, dear.
That's not the girl you
picked up in the bar last night.
No, she delivered the pizza
to me and the girl I picked up
at the bar last night.
Well, I hope you gave her
a good tip.
Nah, she didn't come
in 30 minutes or less.
Whoa.
(imitates siren)
Fashion Police.
Pull over.
What?
The reason I stopped you
is it appears
your style has expired.
You don't like
this sweater?
I thought it
looked good.
Have you been drinking, sir?
This coming
from a man
who looks like he's been
tented for termites.
(doorbell rings)
Lyndsey.
Hi, Alan.
Uh, did we have
plans for tonight?
No, I was
in the area
and I thought I'd surprise
you with a booty call.
Oh. Wow.
Well, normally that would
be delightful, but...
Wait.
You're wearing cologne
and your one good shirt.
You have a date.
Oh, no, I-I wouldn't
call it a date,
you know, uh, um...
Walden met this woman,
and she's got a friend,
really ugly.
Mm-hmm.
(chuckling)
You know how
they say, you know,
people were beaten
with the ugly stick?
Well...
well, you know,
if you took a bunch
of the ugly sticks
and built an ugly house,
when this girl
walked by,
the house would
call her ugly.
Alan, relax.
You're allowed to date.
Oh, really?
Of course. I mean,
I have a boyfriend.
Oh, thank God, 'cause this girl is
actually way hot.
(laughs)
I mean, you know,
not as hot as you,
but, you know,
young-hot.
You've been hot
a lot longer.
I'm gonna go.
You sure you're
okay with this?
I'm sure.
Go have fun.
Oh, that's my good old Lyndsey.
I didn't mean "old"!
(imitates siren)
Idiot Police.
Pull over.
God, it's great out here.
The stars look amazing.
Yeah, without the lights
from the city, they really pop.
That's why you can see
Orion's Belt so clearly.
Uh, you know, if you
look under Orion's Belt,
uh, you can see
his Little Dipper.
(laughs)
Oh, my God,
you are so bad.
(laughing)
You're into astronomy?
'Cause I've been
into astronomy
since I went
to space camp.
Also about the same
time I got into
getting my ass kicked
at school.
I always wanted
to go to space camp.
Nerd!
I prefer "geek."
Wh-What about you,
Laurie?
Are you into
astronomy?
Yep, I'm a Virgo.
But I'm not a virgin.
Both good signs
for me.
So, uh, how did you become
a princess, anyway?
Oh, I get that a lot.
(whispering):
I'm not a real princess.
I'm also not
a real redhead.
You'll find
that out later.
No way, it must be great
being a princess.
Yeah, for the most part.
What's not so great
are the pervy dads
who are trying
to cop a feel.
The other day I was like,
"Do that again,
you're gonna find out
where else
my glass slipper fits."
Is it weird that
that turns me on?
Is it weird
that's why I told you?
So, hey, would you girls like
a little more champagne?
Oh, I would!
(laughs)
I love champagne.
And puppies!
Um, what's the magic word?
Oh... boobs!
Ah, the kids must love you.
I really like Jill.
I mean, she's fun, she's
beautiful, she's smart.
And I really like Laurie--
she's fun,
she's beautiful, she's stupid.
So, uh, what's the next move?
I'm gonna take Jill up to my
room and show her my telescope.
What am I gonna do?
There's nothing
in my room to show Laurie.
Yes, there is.
You have a couch
that turns into a bed.
She'll be amazed.
Okay, open your eyes.
Oh, my God!
Where'd the couch go?
Ah-ah-ah!
A magician never
reveals his secrets.
That's amazing.
And for my next trick,
I'm going to make
my penis disappear.
(gasps)
I'll need a volunteer
from the audience.
Ooh, pick me, pick me!
Um...
(laughs)
(cell phone ringing)
(grunts)
Oh, sorry, um...
Uh, my mom.
No problem.
I'll go put in a condom.
Uh, uh, that's not how...
You know what? Great.
Lyndsey?
Alan? Thanks for calling.
You called me.
Oh, that's good 'cause I was
just gonna call you.
Lyndsey, you're drunk.
Alan, you're boring.
Okay, I'm gonna go.
Whoa, whoa, wait!
Just one thing.
Remember when I told you
I was okay
with you dating other people?
Uh-huh.
Well, I'm not.
You're not?
(door opens)
I'm ready
for your next trick.
Can I call you back? I'm...
going into a tunnel.
So, what do you think
of your princess?
I think I am enchanted.
And engorged.
Well, let's see
about giving this story
a happy ending.
Uh, can you hold on
for a second?
Oh.
Oh, oh!
Uh, not what I meant.
But... big thumbs-up.
Oh, oh!
It was a...
It was a metaphorical thumbs-up.
Uh, and-and you work
with children.
Is everything all right?
Uh, yeah, yeah, uh, uh,
can you just, uh,
hang on a minute?
I've got to freshen up.
Oh, the bathroom's right there.
Yeah, no, I have to...
poop.
Okay.
Check out this star.
Is that the guy from Survivor?
Yeah, Jeff Probst.
He's naked and cooking...
bacon?
Yeah, he does it every night.
It's a regular bacon
and sausage fest.
And why do you watch?
Uh, there's not much on TV.
But... more importantly...
I think he wants me to.
Well, maybe if there
was something better
for you to look at?
Oh.
(loud knocking)
ALAN:
Walden! Walden!
I know! Probst is cooking.
ALAN:
No, no! It-it's an emergency.
I'm sorry, it's...
Mm-hmm.
What?
Lyndsey called me.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Why didn't you say that
from the beginning?
(loud knocking)
She told me she is not okay
with me dating someone else.
She has a boyfriend, okay?
What she's doing to you is not fair.
So what should I do?
You should do what every boy in
America has dreamed about doing,
and go downstairs
and bang the Little Mermaid.
You're right.
A bush in the hand
and all that.
Well, I'd tell you
to go screw her brains out,
but somebody already
beat you to it.
(cell phone ringing)
Aw, great.
Um...
Hi, Lynds.
No, no, you have, uh,
nothing to apologize for.
I-I sent her home.
You left a surprise for me?
Oh...
you didn't have to do that.
Surprise!
Lyndsey?
Yeah.
I felt bad
about ruining your date
so I wanted to make it up to you.
Oh.
LAURIE:
Alan, where are you?
Who was that?
Oh, uh, that's just
a TV show I'm watching.
It's called...
Alan, Where Are You?
Um, well,
you know what?
Thanks for dropping by,
but I'm gonna have
to take a rain check.
So I will see you soon.
Are you done pooping?
(groans)
Whoop!
Who the hell is this?
Ooh, I'm so sorry.
Is this your mom?
Bitch, you are gonna die!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on,
hold on, hold on, hold on.
I thought you said
you sent the slut home.
How does she know I'm a slut?
Okay, okay, this-this is just
a classic misunderstanding.
It-it's like a bad episode
of Alan, Where Are You?
You lied to me!
I was just about
to kick her out.
You were about to kick me out?
I wasn't. I was.
I wasn't.
WALDEN:
Hey.
What is going on?
Alan's mom thinks I'm a slut.
Alan's cheating on me.
Uh, you have a boyfriend!
Now who's the slut?
Ooh, ooh!
Okay, maybe...
we should just get
our things and go.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Don't-don't get your things.
I like your things.
I haven't even
seen your things.
I really think we
should call it a night.
No, Alan, do something!
Uh, o-okay, what we're
gonna do is...
(retching)
Whoa!
Whoa.
Must have vagina!
Morning.
Hey, sorry for puking
in the living room last night.
What?
I think I just drank
a little too much.
Oh, th-that wasn't you.
That was Lyndsey.
Oh, awesome!
Guess who doesn't have
a drinking problem.
Morning.
Sorry again about last night.
You know what?
I really liked Jill.
What happened was
out of my control.
No, it wasn't!
This whole non-relationship
relationship thing
you have going on
with Lyndsey is ridiculous.
And now it's affecting me.
You owe me a princess
and an area rug.
What happened?
I'll tell you what happened. Nothing.
The only person who got hot,
drunk sex last night
was Lyndsey's boyfriend.
Actually...
Okay, fine.
Him and you.
Well...
Aw, damn it!
(doorbell rings)
Lyndsey, can we talk?
Sure, I've been puking
at 20-minute intervals.
So... you got eight minutes.
Look, a-about last night...
I-I am really sorry.
I-I was totally out of line.
It's just...
I started picturing you
with some other girl
and I got so jealous.
I mean...
isn't that crazy?
It's you.
Ouch, there was an iron fist
in that velvet glove.
Um, look.
I want to be with you.
And this whole thing with me,
you and Larry
just isn't working anymore.
So what are you saying?
I'm saying
it's-it's either me or him.
Well, it's not that simple.
I can't just choose.
I guess you already did.
Good-bye, Lyndsey.
Alan, wait.
Yeah?
I-I choose you.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh!
Oh, you make me so happy.
You make me happy, too.
So, you gonna
break up with Larry?
Yes.
Aw, great.
It feels so good
to be back in your arms.
Yeah...
Hold on.
(retching)
Oh, hold my hair!
Oh, it's just like old times.
(yells)
♪ Men. ♪
Wow.
Yeah, wow.
That was, uh...
Boring.
Very.
What was missing?
Larry.
Knowing we're not supposed
to have sex made it way hotter.
It really did.
You think maybe Larry
would take you back?
I haven't told him yet.
Smart.
Hey.
Now that we both know that
Larry's still in the picture,
maybe we should try again.
Okay.
I promise this time
I won't fake my orgasm.
Oh, then neither will I.
Walden.
Can you help me, miss?
A beautiful woman fled my house
last night and the only clue
I have to her identity
is this shoe she left behind.
Oh, that's very sweet,
but this isn't a good time.
Why, is it...?
Do I smell bacon?
You should go.
Everything okay, babe?
JILL:
I just need a second.
All right.
Bacon's ready.
I'm sorry.
Damn you, Probst.
♪ Men. ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man